spotebi.com 2019-01-18

# Privacy Policy

The following privacy policy informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of the personal information we receive from the users of our website.

#### What non-personally identifiable information do we collect?

Like many other website operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website (“log data”). This log data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

Our website uses **Google Analytics** , a web analytics service provided by Google Inc., to collect log data. Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, that help us analyze how users use our website. We use this information to keep track of your preferences, personalize your experience and improve our website. To opt-out of Analytics for the web, visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). To learn more read “[How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)“.

We also use third party advertisements, **Google Adsense** and **AdThrive** , to support us and serve ads on our website. These advertisers may use technology such as cookies or the DoubleClick cookie, to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCiihoNKO5HSksbfUtMCw-_gcky3pENEm3Ukdyub24aX2MkFYW0Hxz4FUx9DdISIKkIdgNO5QolRtAUaovpwGjljekyxVBw2OQjoBB5fqO8b7-7rPapn10LrzZ0baTD381_g-45IRDSy8y53t0WDLJUviP9wzmi_n0UhmHsqH7o4iN4IVlk). You can also choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings.

This non-personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### What personally identifiable information do we collect?

While using our website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include but is not limited to, your name, email address, photo, postal address and phone number.

We use **Mad Mimi** , a service operated by Mad Mimi, c/o GoDaddy.com LLC., to collect email addresses and to create, send and track email promotions. We collect this personally identifiable information when you subscribe to our newsletter, purchase a product from our shop or sign up to one of our fitness challenges. We use this information to send you periodic emails, promotions, and updates. Every email contains a link for you to be able to opt-out and unsubscribe to our newsletter and another link named “Preferences” that gives you access to your “Member Details” and allows you to disable email tracking. You can read [Mad Mimi’s privacy policy](https://madmimi.com/legal/privacy) to learn more.

**When you sign up to one of our Fitness Challenges** you may be asked to share personally identifiable information. By signing up to those challenges and answering the weekly quizzes, you’re allowing us to share that personally identifiable information on our website and on our social media platforms. If at any moment you wish to opt-out, email us at contact@spotebi.com and we will respect your decision.

**When you purchase a product or membership from our[Shop](https://www.spotebi.com/shop/)** you will be asked to share personal data. We strongly believe in both minimizing the data we collect and limiting its use and purpose to deliver the services you purchase or interact with. To easily access, view, update, delete or port your personal data, please [sign in to your Account](https://www.spotebi.com/my-account/) and visit “Account Details”. If you make a request to delete your personal data and that data is necessary for the products or services you have purchased, the request will be honored only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual recordkeeping requirements. If you are unable for any reason to access your Account Settings, you may also contact us via email at contact@spotebi.com.

We will not share, sell or rent your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties that work with us, so long as they agree to keep your personally identifiable information confidential. We may also release your personally identifiable information to comply with the law, in the case of an attempted breach of security of our website, or to protect our or others rights, safety or property.

#### How we secure, store and retain your data

We follow generally accepted standards to store and protect the personal data we collect, both during transmission and once received and stored, including utilization of encryption where appropriate.

We retain personal data only for as long as necessary to provide the services you have requested and thereafter for a variety of legitimate legal or business purposes. These might include retention periods:

  * mandated by law, contract or similar obligations applicable to our business operations;
  * for preserving, resolving, defending or enforcing our legal/contractual rights; or
  * needed to maintain adequate and accurate business and financial records.

If you have any questions about the security or retention of your personal data, you can contact us at contact@spotebi.com.

#### Third party links

We may occasionally include third party links on our website. These third party links have their own privacy policies and we encourage you to review them before providing any of them with your personal information. We have no control over and assume no responsibility or liability for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party websites or services.

#### Privacy of children

We will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 18 years of age.

#### Changes to our privacy policy

We may update our privacy policy from time to time and we will post those changes on this page. You are advised to review our privacy policy periodically for any changes.

#### Your consent

By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy.

#### Contact

If you have any questions, please email us at contact@spotebi.com.

Last updated: January 9, 2019
